socialtables.com 2019-11-02

# Social Tables | Privacy Policy

## **Summary of Recent Changes:**

 **What’s new as of [05/30/2019]:** ** **

 **We recently changed our Privacy Policy. The following is a summary of key changes:**

  *  **Additional details on the various types of users who are subject to this Privacy Policy and how we collect and process their data.**
  *  **An explanation of your rights to access, correct, and delete personal information, including how you can exercise those rights.**
  *  **More details as to how we may use personal information and how long we may keep certain data.**
  *  **Further details on Social Tables’ use of cookies and similar technologies.**
  *  **Our legal basis for processing personal data and how long we store the data.**
  *  **Statement and information that our applications are not intended for children under 13 years of age.**

 **Last modified: [05/30/2019]**

##  **Introduction**

Social Tables, Inc. (“Social Tables” “we” or “us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your privacy through our compliance with this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Social Tables collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User” and types of users further defined below) of the <https://www.socialtables.com/> website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Social Tables (collectively referred to as “Applications”).

This policy also describes your data protection rights, including a right to object to some of Social Tables’ processing. The Policy does not apply to information collected by any third party, including through any third-party application or content (including advertising) that links to or is accessible from our Applications or websites.

##  **Table of Contents**

  1.  **Are you a Customer, Customer Business Contact or Visitor**
  2.  **What types of personal data do our Customers collect?**
  3.  **How do our Customers collect personal data?**
  4.  **How do our Customers use personal data?**
  5.  **Does Social Tables use or sell personal data collected by our Customers?**
  6.  **How does Social Tables collect and process personal data from our Customers and their Customer Business Contacts?**
  7.  **What is the legal basis for Social Tables to process personal data from the EEA?**
  8.  **How can a Customer Business Contact access, correct or delete their personal data?**
  9.  **How can a Customer access, correct, or delete their personal data?**
  10.  **How does Social Tables process data from Visitors?**
  11.  **Does Social Tables process information of children under the age of 13?**
  12.  **How we protect your information**
  13.  **What are  Social Tables’ Products?**
  14.  **How does Social Tables publicize changes to its Privacy Policy?**
  15.  **Your acceptance of these terms**
  16.  **Contacting us**

This policy applies to the following classification of individuals that interact with Social Tables:

  * CUSTOMERS: Customers are individuals that are employees or associates of Social Tables’ direct customers (for example, event planners or meeting space providers), including customer personnel that are assigned a login ID and are authorized to access and use our Applications pursuant to an active Social Tables agreement, or under a temporary evaluation license, if available. Additionally, Customers include individuals who self-register to access our Applications.
  * CUSTOMER BUSINESS CONTACTS: Customer Business Contacts are individuals that interact with our Customers through our Applications. These include our Customers’ current and prospective clients, members, attendees, sponsors, exhibitors, marketing partners, hotel guests or other business contacts. For example, Customer Business Contacts include individuals that register for an event organized by a Customer or if a hospitality Customer inputs Customer Business Contacts to help plan an event using one of our Applications to help plan an event.  
  * VISITORS: Individuals that interact with our Sites (for instance, to read about our products and services, download a white paper, or sign up for an online demo), as well as those who attend our marketing events (for instance, our live trainings) and whom we meet at a tradeshow or learn about through a referral from third parties or other external sources.

##  **What types of personal data do our Customers collect?**

Our Applications are flexible and allow our Customers to collect a variety of personal data from and about their Customer Business Contacts, including name, organization, title, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, social media account ID, credit or debit card number and other information including but not limited to dietary preferences, interests, opinions, activities, age, gender, education and occupation.

For a more detailed list of our Applications, please refer to the “ _What are Social Tables' Products_ ” section at the end of this Privacy Policy. Our use of personal information collected through our Applications shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which our Customers have engaged Social Tables.

If you do not agree with our policies and practices, you may choose not to use our Applications.

##  **How do our Customers collect personal data?**

  * When Customer Business Contacts voluntarily and explicitly enter personal data into our Applications.
  * When our Customers enter Customer Business Contacts into our Applications, when permitted, including by having a legitimate business interest or obtaining explicit consent from a Customer Business Contact.
  * Automatically, as Customer Business Contacts interact with our Applications, using commonly used information gathering technologies such as cookies. For additional information about these technologies, see the section below titled “ _How does Social Tables use cookies and similar technologies?_ “.

##  **How do our Customers use personal data?**

If a Customer Business Contact chooses to use our Applications to conduct business with a Customer (for example: register for or check into an event or use our event design tools), any information provided in connection with that interaction will be transferred to, and under the control of, the Customer.

Customers will also have access to information (including personal data and Application usage data) related to how Customer Business Contact interact with the Applications they use. In such instance, the Customers act as data controllers towards the Customer Business Contact, under the European Economic Area (“EEA”) data protection laws.  Therefore, Social Tables cannot and does not take responsibility for the privacy practices of Customers.

The information practices of our Customers are governed by their privacy policies. We encourage Customer Business Contacts to review the Customers’ privacy policies to understand their practices and procedures.

Social Tables does not use personal data of our Customer Business Contacts for any purposes other than to provide services that our Customers have contracted us to provide through our Applications, as noted below, or as required by law. Social Tables does not sell personal data of our Customer Business Contacts.

We collect personal data from our Customers in order to facilitate communication and delivery of the Applications that our Customers are interested in or contract us to provide. For example, we may collect Customer contact information, whether through the execution of a contract, use of our services, a form on our website, an interaction with our sales or customer support team, sign up for an event, or a response to one of our surveys or marketing emails. We may also collect credit card information (e.g., credit card number and expiration date, billing address, etc.) or other customary bank information needed for billing and payment purposes.

We may record Customer telephone calls made to our Client Services team for legitimate business interests related to providing Customer support, compliance with laws, training, and quality assurance. We retain such recordings until 90 days after the date of recording.

We collect Customer usage information about how our Customers interact with our Applications. This includes which webpages you visit, what you click on, when you perform certain actions, what language preference you have, what you buy, and so on.

We process Customer’s and their Customer Business Contacts’ personal data in the following manner:

  * To disclose to our affiliates for the purpose of providing services to our Customers and their Customer Business Contacts.
  * To disclose to contractors, service providers, and other third parties as reasonably necessary or prudent to provide, maintain and support our Applications for our Customers and their Customer Business Contacts, such as, for example, payment processors and data center or Web hosting providers.  ** _Social Tables does not share, sell or trade any information with such third parties for promotional purposes._**
  * To deliver the Applications that our Customer has contracted us to provide. Some examples include:
    * If a Customer or Customer Business Contact communicates with our customer service team, we use the information to ensure the proper level of support is given.
    * If a Customer or Customer Business Contact uses credentials for other third-party applications to login to Social Tables, we confirm their information with the third-party application.
    * If a Customer or Customer Business Contact edits information within the application, we save the time, date and interactions in order for them to be read by other users.
    * If a Customer or Customer Business Contact uses one of our Applications to pay for event fees or other products and services using their credit cards, we will pass the credit card information to payment card processors to validate the payment information and complete the transactions.
  * To deliver to a third party in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, recapitalization, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all Social Tables’ assets, whether as a continuing operating business or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal data held by Social Tables about our Customers and Customer Business Contacts is among the assets transferred.
  * For our internal business purposes that include administering access and use of our Applications, data analysis, securely identifying Customers upon logging onto an Application, enhancing or modifying our Applications, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, billing for Services, and operating our business.
  * To send periodic emails. We may use the email address to send Customers information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If a User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via the contact information at the bottom of this policy.
  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate:  (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; and (c) to protect against or identify fraudulent transactions.
  * For other purposes when Customer Business Contacts provide explicit consent.

We aggregate and anonymize information about (i) Customers and Customer Business Contacts, and (ii) the use of our Applications in order to improve our Applications and to create benchmark and other business intelligence products. None of the aggregated and anonymized information contain personal data (i.e., does not identify any individual).

For individuals that are from the European Economic Area (EEA), our legal basis for collecting and using their personal information will be our legitimate interest where the processing is in our, or a third party's, legitimate interests and not overridden by the individual’s data protection interests, or fundamental rights and freedoms. These interests are to provide individuals with access to the Applications and features of the Applications; to send them information they have requested; to ensure the security of our Applications by trying to prevent unauthorised or malicious activities; or to enforce compliance with our terms of use, contracts and other policies. In some EEA countries, we are relying on consent as a legal basis for using data for marketing purposes.

In various countries, including countries in the EEA, upon their request, Customer Business Contacts have the right to access their personal data and, if necessary, have it amended, deleted or restricted. Customer Business Contacts can also ask for some types of personal data to be delivered to them, or another organization they nominate, in a structured and machine-readable format. 

Where we process your personal data on the basis of your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent. See the Social Tables contact section below. The withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. Customer Business Contacts also have the right to complain to a supervisory authority for data protection in the country where they live, or where they work – although we hope that we can assist with any queries or concerns you have about our use of your personal data.

We process Customer Business Contacts data under the direction of our Customers and has no direct control or ownership of the personal data we process. Customers are responsible for complying with any regulations or laws requiring notice, disclosure, or obtaining consent prior to transferring the data to Social Tables for processing purposes. Any Customer Business Contact that seeks to access, correct or delete data, should direct their query to the Customer. If the Customer requests Social Tables to remove the personal data of a Customer Business Contact to comply with data protection regulations, Social Tables will process this request within 30 days.

We will not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. In such instances, we will inform the Customer about the legal obligations that prevent us from fulfilling the request.

##  **How can a Customer access, correct, or delete their personal data?**

Customers have the same rights to access, correct or delete their personal data as do Customer Business Contacts, as outlined in section “How can a Customer Business Contact access, correct or delete their personal data?”

Any Customer that seeks to access, correct or delete data, can do so by submitting a request on our website at https://www.cvent.com/gdpr-personal-data-request. Social Tables will process this request within 30 days.

We will not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. In such instances, we will inform the Customer about the legal obligations that prevent us from fulfilling the request.

We will maintain an audit history of any requests to access, correct or delete personal information to maintain a record of compliance with regulatory requirements.

 **How does Social Tables use cookies and similar technologies?**

 ** _Cookies and Web Beacons_**

We use cookies or similar automatic data collection technologies as individuals interact with our Applications to collect certain information about their equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Applications, such as the date and time you access our Applications, length of time you spend on our Applications, websites that linked to our Applications or websites linked from our Applications, the resources and content that you access and use on the Applications.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, such as your IP Address, computer type, screen resolution, language, Internet browser type and version. 

 ** _Below are the technologies we use for automatic data collection.  We do not use any of these technologies to collect information from Customer Business Contacts for marketing or advertising purposes._**

  *  **Browser Cookies.**   A cookie is a small file placed on a computer hard drive.  Web browsers can be configured to restrict or entirely block cookies, to configure cookie notification settings and/or to delete cookies already present on the browser or device.  Information on how to do this is provided by the web browser’s help/reference section. Limiting or restricting certain types of cookies may prevent a Customer or Customer Business Contact from using certain portions of our Applications, depending on how the browser settings are configured. Unless the browser setting has been adjusted so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when the browser interacts with our Applications.  For more information about cookies and how to disable them, see  _[www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)_.
  *  **Session Cookies and Persistent Cookies.  **A "session" cookie lasts for a single browser session only and is deleted when the user closes the web browser. Session cookies allow website operators to link the actions of a user during a browser session.  A "persistent" cookie remains on the user’s device (even while powered off) until it expires or is deleted.  A persistent cookie will be reactivated when a user returns to the website which posted the cookie. We use persistent cookies to help customize your web experience when you return to a web page or our website.Neither of these cookies can read or access other cookies or any data from a user’s hard drive. Further, neither of these cookies alone will personally identify a user; however, a cookie will recognize a user’s individual web browser or device through an IP Address, browser version, operating system and other information, and individuals who log in to their Social Tables accounts will be individually identifiable to particular Applications using session cookies.
  *  **Web Beacons.**   Pages in our Applications and our e-mails will contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags and single-pixel gifs).  Web beacons differ from cookies in that the information is not stored on your hard drive, but invisibly embedded on web pages or in email.  Web beacons permit us to track online movements of web users, for example: to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).  This enables us to provide a website experience more tailored to our Users’ preferences and interests.

  *  **Flash Cookies.  ** Certain features of our services will use local storage, such as "Flash cookies" to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Websites.  Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. If you do not want Flash cookies stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash cookie storage using the tools contained in the Website Storage Settings Panel available at the following  _[link](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html)_.

 ** _Advertising_**

Social Tables works with [AdRoll retargeting](https://www.adroll.com/), who uses technology such as web beacons and cookies to collect data about our website usage and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. Data recorded through the use of this technology is aggregated and shared with us. No personally identifiable information about you is collected or shared by AdRoll with Social Tables. You can opt-out of AdRoll and their partners by visiting [this link.](https://www.adrollgroup.com/privacy)

We also use other third parties (such as LinkedIn, Google, YouTube) to serve advertisements that may be of interest to you on other websites. For more information and the ability to control your preferences, please visit:

 _[http://preferences-mgr.truste.com](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/)_ ,  
_<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>_  and   
_<http://www.aboutads.info/>_  
_<https://policies.google.com/privacy/partners>_

If you are located in Switzerland or the European Union, please click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

 ** _Third Party Analytics Providers_**

We use third party analytics providers, including Google, Adobe, Mixpanel, Mouseflow and others, to collect information about the usage of our Applications and enable us to improve how these Applications work.  The information allows us to see the overall patterns of usage on the Applications, helps us record any difficulties you have with the Applications, shows us whether our advertising is effective or not, and allows us to use responses to advertisements to optimize ad performance.  Google Analytics, Adobe and Mixpanel use cookies and other similar technologies to collect information about the usage of our Applications and to report website trends to us, without storing any personal data on external third-party analytics provider platforms.  See below for more information, or to opt out of these practices:

  * You may opt-out of Google Analytics by clicking  _[here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)_. 
  * You may opt-out of Adobe’s data aggregation and analysis about your use of the Applications by clicking on this  _[link](https://ssc.cvent.com/optout.html)_. 
  * You may opt-out of Mixpanel’s practices by visiting  _<https://mixpanel.com/optout/>_. 
  * Mouseflow collects information related to mouse clicks, mouse movements, scroll behavior, and/or keystroke activity, but it does not collect personally identifiable information on our behalf or track users’ browsing habits across other websites that do not use Mouseflow.  You can learn more about Mouseflow’s practices by visiting  _<http://mouseflow.com/privacy>_.

We process Visitor data separately and distinctly from the way we process Customer and Customer Business Contact data. By visiting our websites, attending our marketing events or providing us with your personal information, Visitors consent to the collection, processing and storage of their personal information as described in this section.

 ** _Visitor Personal Data Collected_**

Social Tables collects personal data including name, title, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, social media account ID, company information (including financial and billing information when purchasing our services), survey responses, message board posts, chat messages, contest entries, and promotional enquiries. We use this information to provide you with additional details about our services, conduct research, provide whitepapers, or to contact you after your visit.

We also collect personal data from third party sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, and social media platforms.

Additionally, we collect personal data from cookies and similar technologies to collect information about the pages Visitors view, links Visitors click on, Visitors’ web browser information, Visitors’ IP address and other actions Visitors may take when accessing our websites. For additional information about our use of these technologies and how to control them, see “ _Cookies and similar technologies_ “ section below.

 **Social Tables’ Use of Visitor Personal Data Collected**

We process Visitor personal data to:

  * Analyze how our websites are accessed;

  * Personalize your browsing experience and present products or features that may be more applicable to you;
  * Identify website technical problems;
  * Discover, investigate and remediate fraudulent or illegal activity;
  * Transmit notices related to product, service, or policy changes;
  * Respond to your product and service inquiries;
  * Send you information such as product announcements, newsletters, whitepapers, other relevant offers, and upcoming promotions or events (where required, dependent on jurisdiction, we will seek and obtain your explicit consent before sending marketing emails);
  * Plan and host Social Tables corporate events, host online forums and social networks in which Visitors may participate;
  * Analyse, score and identify new prospects;
  * Create tailored advertising, sales and promotional programs; and
  * Bill customers for our services and assess the financial capability of prospective customers to afford Social Tables’ solutions.

If you wish to remove yourself from communications about Social Tables, please click here: <https://www.cvent.com/subscriptionmanagement>.

 ** _Storing of Visitor Personal Data_**

Where we process Visitor personal data for marketing purposes or with Visitor consent, we process the data until the Visitor asks us to stop. It typically takes up to 30 days to implement such a request. Social Tables will not retain Visitor personal data longer than the statutory retention period permitted in the local jurisdictions where our services are marketed and provided. We also keep a record of when Visitors have asked us not to send direct marketing or to process Visitor data indefinitely so that we can respect the Visitor’s request in the future.

 ** _Sharing of Visitor Data_**

Social Tables may share information with third party service providers contracted to provide services on our behalf as well as third parties who resell Social Tables services.

Social Tables may also engage with business partners to jointly offer products, services or other programs such as webinars or whitepapers and from time to time, we may share personal data if you purchase or show interest in any jointly-offered products or services.

Social Tables will only share personal data of Visitors who attend a Social Tables marketing event with third parties if a) the Visitor explicitly consents, b) the Visitor permits their badge to be scanned, or c) it is permissible under applicable law.

 ** _Access, correct or delete Visitor data_**

Visitors have the same rights to access, correct or delete their personal data as do our Customers, as outlined in section “ _How can a Customer access, correct or delete your personal data?_ ”

Any Visitor that seeks to access, correct or delete data, can do so by submitting a request on our website at  _<https://www.cvent.com/gdpr-personal-data-request>_. Social Tables will process this request within 30 days.

We will not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. In such instances, we will inform the Visitor about the legal obligations that prevent us from fulfilling the request. 

We will maintain an audit history of any requests to access, correct or delete personal information to maintain a record of compliance with regulatory requirements.

 **Cookies and similar technologies**

All practices related to cookies and their usage described in section “ _How does Social Tables use cookies and similar technologies”  _also applies to Visitors when they interact with our websites.

Our Applications are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not directly solicit or collect personal data from children under 13.  If you are under 13, do not (i) use or provide any information on these Applications or on or through any of its features, (ii) register to use any of our Applications, (iii) make any purchases through our Applications, (iv) use any of the interactive or public comment features of our Applications or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you will use.

##  **How we protect your information**

We use a variety of organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect personal data within our organization.  We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with the Contact Information section below.

 **Event Sales:**

  * Sales & Catering CRM Software
  * Interactive Lead Capture
  * Lead Intelligence Software
  * Sales Enablement Software
  * Event Proposal Software

 **Event Services:**

  * Event Diagramming Software
  * Event Collaboration Tools
  * Value-Add Planner Tools

 **Free Planner Tools**

  * Event Seating Software
  * Event Check-In Software
  * Pocket Planner App

We will update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this website thirty (30) days prior to the changes becoming effective, or by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) seven (7) days prior to the changes becoming effective. However, any changes to the Privacy Policy are effective immediately upon publication for new Visitors, Customers, and Customer Business Contacts. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

##  **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Social Tables  
1325 G Street, NW, 3rd Floor, Washington, DC 20005  
+1 (877) 973-2863
